<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cwille97</title><link>https://cwille97.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on cwille97</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:29:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cwille97.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About this website</title><link>https://cwille97.github.io/posts/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:29:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cwille97.github.io/posts/about/</guid><description>What is this website? This is my personal space on the web
How did you make this? I built this with Hugo using the terminal theme by panr
Why does this website use analytics? I added privacy preserving analytics from TelemetryDeck in order to get an idea of how many views my website is getting and where it is being linked from. I do not user any type of user identifier, and the only additional data I am currently sending in my payload is the document.</description><content>&lt;h1 id="what-is-this-website">What is this website?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>This is my personal space on the web&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="how-did-you-make-this">How did you make this?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I built this with &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/">Hugo&lt;/a> using the &lt;a href="https://github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal">terminal theme&lt;/a> by &lt;a href="https://github.com/panr">panr&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="why-does-this-website-use-analytics">Why does this website use analytics?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I added privacy preserving analytics from &lt;a href="https://telemetrydeck.com/">TelemetryDeck&lt;/a> in order to get an idea of how many views my website is getting and where it is being linked from. I do not user any type of user identifier, and the only additional data I am currently sending in my payload is the &lt;code>document.referrer&lt;/code> parameter. If you wish to opt out, you can press the button at the bottom of this page and your preference will be saved in local storage (which means if you do something to clear local storage, this preference will need to be set again). Alternatively, you can disable JavaScript.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>